[Music]
We're trying a new meditation today.
Use this afternoon meditation.
Everyone has problems. Tomorrow you
might have to meet a friend.
You can prepare in the morning.
[Music] There are
two classic ways
to obtain the Protector. One is register.
The first is an exchange format. He himself
with the other. And the other
meditation is the Mother Meditation. It's
a famous text that's in your reading.
I felt the text as I
expected. In the monastery, they had
a competition once a year with the
others, and this competition
rotated through the different cities.
Kappa is the greatest one can be because
[Music] I
drove to the greatest college monastery. I've been there for
twelve hours.
Simply put, if you drive on an American
road, it will take an hour.
I would have nothing,
and I stayed home.
This is the poster he made.
When I slept in his house,
he was reborn. He was a young one.
He was a great bug
collector, and I searched around internally for ages,
and I found this book.
I found many great ones here.
I have a beautiful book, a beautiful one.  I
found a picture of him that I'll
show you. He then had a long meeting
with the Pope. I don't really know who it
is, but I found it in his
personal writings. They made
me search for it.
It's complicated, a combined
meditation of meditation and
exchange meditation. Of
course, let yourselves learn what it is,
then see how it goes.
I don't know how it will work,
but if he had it in his personal
writings, then it's
probably very cool.
Let's try it.
[Music]
First, try out what the
problem is. Let's try it. Relax your
fingers. Relax his eyelids. It's hard to
relax his eyelids. You have to
try this. A slight smile, also
give them a little bit of the blame.
Then go back, go together. Do
n't forget the option. Would you be the
chance beyond the horizon?
Then come to your breaths. Extra breathing moves.
I think there's
something with ten. We had
six in one breath. Make extra
exhalation moves.
Choose someone you know, or the gap
says hate, who has problems. Through
thirteen different steps in this
meditation, in your choice of people who have
problems, we...
To choose people who
are closer to us, not to choose the
development further away from the first job
in the dong, a longer visitation, it is
to choose a person whose problem
you might think about people
who normally want to,
but here, first step,
let's learn the concrete, try meditation on
someone because you don't know the viruses
or whom we don't like so much.
[Music]
Everyone has problems, so maybe
today we can do a meditation
for someone who is currently
experiencing bombs in the war, so maybe
someone is suffering from food, sitting too close in
the class, but someone who
has problems or someone where a relative has
died,
a student in this class
flew from China to Los Angeles,
one of his parents died and he
flew back to Los Angeles,
so he found out, bought the ticket
and flew back again, would be someone you know,
someone who
is not so close
or maybe someone you would like to make
a person.
[Music] Here
comes the second stage of this
completely combined meditation,
thinking about how this person
we are meditating on, your mother was brazen,
can  It in one of the past lives
thinks about this person
you might not know so well.
Let's understand that they, and that
a user, was with you and around you.
Your mother was as close as a mother
in this life.
The third parting is
trying to think about the thesis, thinking
about the beautiful things
this person gave you as a mother, for example, in
life,
or that they carried you for nine months
and warned you were tired. It drops from 990.
We had nine months to
think about your birth. If it was
a past life, then your
birthday was certainly more dangerous. Also,
they are now on what can be dangerous
for Dido. Meditated, it was about weight to
die,
and then they taught you everything.
You need to know how to be when you hear about how to live
a life,
go to school, talk,
think about all these things that
this person did for you. It
tries to keep you in your mind.
Logically, what they did for you behind the
past.
[Music]
The fourth step is
thinking that I pay them back.
[Music]
I  I would be a strange person, I'm following
my motto, I wouldn't give that back,
so this person who edits the dom
thinks about giving them back,
how to let things come to them
when she
was your mother,
when we think about the other system,
we meditate on it, we
have the same rights, the same
opportunities, the same right to earn money,
should take on the same expenses for
others, to
ask for money, to be lucky is not fair
if I think about my luck
more and am there more for my luck,
for others, that's
step number 6, I could
continue as I have done so far, taking care
more and not for this
person, I know myself, if I
do that, something would be wrong in the
world, I would
treat myself better than the other person,
something would be wrong there, it's quite good
that I have helped other people,
now the country can at least, if
I take care, then with one
click something will happen, if my whole
life, if I take care of myself more
and I don't and I don't care about the
other person, that's  It
would be wrong to think that the joy and happiness in
my life revolve around being able to care for
other people.
Helping others to
be happy isn't really about me. If
I focus on myself to
be happy, then my life will get worse and worse, and I'll become
increasingly
unhappy.
It's in my own interest to
care more and more about others and less about myself. It's
a logic that
helps others. This person was
n't so interested before, but won't gain
a little strength to help this person.
If that's true, then I will get
more and more of what
I want. Instead of ignoring their situation
and not caring about
myself, which is a lose-
lose situation, I use the time
I spend caring for this person.
If it was a camera, then things will go back to normal.
I make them happy, then
I make myself happy. It's a win-win
situation.
If I
focus more on the other person over the years, and
not less,
I will get more and more of what
I've dreamed of.
Let's think about it.
[Music]
Eight of the meditation thinks about
what would happen in the world if they were like that.  I would
think if everyone
cared for other people,
even if no word is true,
the forests could become artificial teeth. The most
wonderful thing we can do is ask,
and in this world, it's to take care of other
people, and especially
Timo, whom we might not know so well.
Then think about how
right it is to follow these laws of the cadre
and to care for others
equally.
We would then have a wonderful result
in this world if we all did that.
In the ninth grade, we exchange ideas with
the other house.
I think that after that, this person wants me to
see them, and I put myself in their
persona.
I put myself in the
other person's body, and I look at myself. Do I feel
about this? Maybe
I don't know the person so well. Maybe
I don't like the person. We've been
trying since yesterday to
put our bodies in theirs and see what it feels like. What it feels like
when
they aren't treated equally and
care more about themselves than about me.
Happiness: put yourself in the
other person's body, and juicy. I
think you have us
thinking about what hurts them, what
problems they have.  have and I want to take away
the pain, gather,
maybe the main problem of the
main markets is the pain that they believe
we don't love them, that could be
painful, in
life we ​​refund the actual tong
ren meditation of the ceiling, imagine
the darkness in their heart and
maybe this dark darkness is
the feeling about it when we don't
care about them, imagine this pain,
this no pain in their hearts
as a black smoke, does
n't care and not like it
cares about itself and that hurts, to
realize that hurts,
let's gather that, let's
gather the black hole in the heart,
March in the pee, or that is a
wonderful illustrated, imagine in the heart, imagine
in our hearts.
[Music]
Has someone, can you, then sir, and
someone, is that someone urgently
imagine,
powerful, who in Schwarzenau, the goings-on in the
house, his shortness out,
we will, so about both names, he has
from Poland,
because inhaling is like a pump of the
alliance,
that brings the dead one out of the
heart,
I want  Not that you, even though
I have this sadness, I do
n't want the AC/DC to keep you every time
you have one. More darkness
comes out of the nose, out of the body,
like you shoot it out of his body through
the nose. The lighter
they feel, and they don't know why. It's
easier when you
shoot their problems out of the body.
I bring this darkness in front of my
nose, because I would have to anticipate. T to
31, three partners come down the throat
and touch the trend. Someone on
the lotus, and there's nothing. Looks and
is destroyed. It's complete with this moment.
They feel so happy. All these
problems because the pain in the heart that
people ignore me and don't come.
I'm happy. They care. It's gone because
the media set it as his golden and
immediately for the children. It's that they
wanted to send the light into the...
through the nose are the holes. That's
level 11, and I send hearts, the knowledge
that Michael loves them and cares for them. She regrets
the old mistakes,
and he tries to
negotiate right away. All  Treating people equally,
he has supplied you so far, not
giving others anything, or the
love he gives himself, lots of
golden light.
The field is now the twelfth stage of the thirteen
stages.
[Music]
I have everything as I can be,
then only that is a lot of work, with that there are
many problems, how much time it
takes and a lot of attention. There are
many people who need my help.
I can say that I treat them all equally,
but it looks very difficult.
Twelve of the stages is a decision to make
in your heart. I will do that, I will try.
I am like a
mother who knows many. My mother, who has
many children, has a lot of money,
but she has shaped me and
says nothing. I don't know how she
can do that.
She says, "I will find a way. It will be
hard.
I have a lot to do. There are many
people who don't need it, but I
will find a way to take care of everyone.
I will work really hard.
I will not give up. I will take care of
everything. Summer area, how I will take care of
them. I will try. I will
not give up. I will not
avoid this. I will take care of everyone.  It
takes
13 levels, which is actually the best way to
care for others. It's about being a good
role model, a joyful
person, a happy person, even
when I have problems, when
I'm tired, when I have too much to
do. But if I stay happy and
free, have a big smile, and
always have time for people, this
virus will spread, the
laughter will spread to a group.
I will be the example, and that's
how I can help other people.
I will be tough, but in my meditation
and with yoga, with my studies,
I will be an example of my person
in this short life.
I will be my hope for other
people.
I will be a good person who
treats all people equally, and that is politics.
I will be a good example.
I will see you again soon. I
care, and I won't worry you.
Then you can open your eyes and
stretch.